<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<slaves>
	<slave id="11">
		<name>Homeless girl</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>Choosing between the street and slavery had to be a nightmare, hope she's happy now.</desc>
		<quote>You used to be so lonely.</quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="12">
		<name>Asian slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>This girl made a dark deal with yakuza to become an idol. And they kept words, her photo is visible in all good dairies.</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="13">
		<name>Voluntary slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>The slavery is so widespread in the society that, when a request is made, there is always a person to change his life.</desc>
		<quote>Sacrifice me.</quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="22">
		<name>Russian slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>This girl was sold by her parent to the local bratva for clearing a debt. Who knows what she suffered before finishing at your service …</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="23">
		<name>Mutant slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>This girl was fed mutagenic since her childhood, no wonder she is over 8 feet and is able to raise 3 tons.</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="24">
		<name>Alien girl</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>A purple skin girl captured in space, her milk may be dangerous.</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="25">
		<name>ESPer slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>A girl driven mad by her extrasensory perception, some say her milk gives visions of the future.</desc>
		<quote>Osorubeki mirai...</quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="26">
		<name>Succubus</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>This girl has been contaminated by dark energy, her milk perverting both body and mind.</desc>
		<quote>When that happened, the good girl who was your mother was destroyed.</quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="32">
		<name>Arabian slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>This girl was sentenced to death for terrorism. Naturally, letting a cute girl die is not in your habits.</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="33">
		<name>Familiar slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>She wanted to be a "Magical girl", maybe asking a dark sorcerer wasn't a good idea. Now, her milk give magic dream.</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="34">
		<name>Elf slave</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>Captured in a magical dimension, her honey taste milk make her extremely popular.</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="35">
		<name>Ghoul girl</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>Born into a family of black mage, it was sure that her attraction to corpses will cause her harm.</desc>
		<quote>This girl has been exposed too young, too long, at too high dose of too dark magic.</quote>
	</slave>
	<slave id="36">
		<name>Seraph</name>
		<effect>Give Milk.</effect>
		<desc>Blessed by the divine light, she started a riot to save her friends, but she losed …</desc>
		<quote></quote>
	</slave>
</slaves>